<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>General &#8211; GOTRAX</title>
	<atom:link href="https://gotrax.com/support/faqs/general/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://gotrax.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 23:30:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	
	<item>
		<title>How Do Hoverboards Work and Function?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-do-hoverboards-work/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 20:23:45 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeff Lawrence]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=13402</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>From the outside, it looks like hoverboards work in mysterious ways, but the truth is these cosmically fun e-rideables are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-do-hoverboards-work/">How Do Hoverboards Work and Function?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>From the outside, it looks like hoverboards work in mysterious ways, but the truth is these cosmically fun e-rideables are built with space-age technology and we&rsquo;ll tell you exactly how a <a href="https://gotrax.com/product/hoverboards/">hoverboard</a> works. The GOTRAX HOVERFLY XL and HOVERFLY ECO self-balancing scooters use electric motors, self-balancing technology, and sensors to detect speed and tilt. Combined, these allow riders to easily stand up, accelerate, turn, and stop simply by shifting your weight.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-do-hoverboards-work/">How Do Hoverboards Work and Function?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Are Electric Scooters Safe?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/electric-scooters-safety/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 22:37:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Diandra]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=9222</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Our top spaceflight engineers had safety in mind when designing our electric scooters. They included features such as a hand [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/electric-scooters-safety/">Are Electric Scooters Safe?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Our top spaceflight engineers had safety in mind when designing our <a href="https://gotrax.com/product/electric-scooters/">electric scooters</a>.  </p>
<p>They included features such as a hand operated braking system, foot controlled stopping system, and bright LED light to ensure that you have the most control when zipping around on your scooter.  However, like with any sport, injuries are still possible.</p>
<p>GOTRAX recommends always wearing appropriate safety gear including helmets and knee/elbow pads, and only operating your scooter in ideal conditions.  We also recommend that those who have conditions that affect their mental and/or physical ability to safely operate the scooter not operate it.  Also, take time to get comfortable with the scooter before you go zipping around on it full speed.  If you follow these basic precautions, you&rsquo;ll enjoy years of incident-free fun on your scooter. </p>
<p>All GOTRAX Commanders are encouraged to closely review the <a href="https://gotrax.com/usermanuals">GLIDER manual</a> and pay attention to all included safety warnings.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/electric-scooters-safety/">Are Electric Scooters Safe?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Are Electric Scooters Legal?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/are-electric-scooters-legal/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 20:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Diandra]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=11057</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>GOTRAX is proud and thrilled to introduce the GLIDER Electric Scooter, a space-age e-scooter that cruises at speeds up to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/are-electric-scooters-legal/">Are Electric Scooters Legal?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>GOTRAX is proud and thrilled to introduce the <a href="https://gotrax.com/shop/electric-scooters/glider/">GLIDER Electric Scooter</a>, a space-age e-scooter that cruises at speeds up to 17 mph with a 250W motor! The GLIDER boasts a LED-backlit display and lunar-bright headlight. Other special features include top performing torque, self-balancing glide, fast fold and release, a smooth and speedy 3-2-1 liftoff, and a top of the line design that is both eye-catching and dynamic.</p>
<p>Safety is another drawing point of the GLIDER Electric Scooter, which offers both a hand-controlled and a foot-activated brake system. </p>
<p>Many of our commander customers simply cannot wait to glide through the GOTRAX Galaxy on their own personal GLIDERs!</p>
<p>Even so, you may be concerned about their city&rsquo;s rules and regulations regarding the ownership and use of electric scooters on public streets and in other areas. You may be wondering if you will be allowed to ride your e-scooter at the park, on the streets, at skate parks and recreational venues, or in your neighborhoods. </p>
<p><strong>And you may even find yourself asking the question, &ldquo;Are electric scooters legal?&rdquo;</strong></p>
<p>Unfortunately, there is no simple answer to this question as the legality of riding an electric scooter depends on a variety of factors.</p>
<p>You should always check your local laws before deciding to buy an electric scooter. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/are-electric-scooters-legal/">Are Electric Scooters Legal?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Do I Charge the Battery in my HOVERFLY Hoverboard?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/charge-battery-hoverfly-hoverboard/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 18:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Diandra]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=10684</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Before charging your HOVERFLY hoverboard, please carefully adhere to all instructions and safety warnings in the Commander&#8217;s Manual to minimize [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/charge-battery-hoverfly-hoverboard/">How Do I Charge the Battery in my HOVERFLY Hoverboard?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Before charging your HOVERFLY hoverboard, please carefully adhere to all instructions and safety warnings in the <a href="https://gotrax.com/usermanuals">Commander&rsquo;s Manual</a> to minimize the risk of personal injury or property damage.</p>
<p>Following the charging instructions will ensure the safety of you and others and the proper operation of your GOTRAX hoverboard.</p>
<ol><li>After removing all packaging, plug the provided charger/adapter into a grounded outlet (100V-240V; 50-60Hz).</li>
<li>Plug the other end of the charger/adapter into the battery charging port of the GOTRAX HOVERFLY located on the back left side of the unit. The indicator light on the charger/adapter will turn to red to confirm that the product is charging.</li>
<li>The GOTRAX HOVERFLY battery will take approximately 1 hour to fully charge.</li>
<li>The GOTRAX HOVERFLY battery is fully charged when the indicator light on the charger/adapter changes from red to green.</li>
<li>Detach the charger/adapter from the GOTRAX HOVERFLY before turning on or operating.</li>
</ol>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/charge-battery-hoverfly-hoverboard/">How Do I Charge the Battery in my HOVERFLY Hoverboard?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Do I Troubleshoot My Hoverboard?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-troubleshoot-hoverboard/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 00:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Diandra]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=10363</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The first step for troubleshooting issues with your hoverboard is to check the Commander&#8217;s Manual. You can find the manual [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-troubleshoot-hoverboard/">How Do I Troubleshoot My Hoverboard?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The first step for troubleshooting issues with your hoverboard is to check the Commander&rsquo;s Manual. You can find the manual for your HOVERFLY model on this page. And it&rsquo;s very likely that the information you need to troubleshoot will be inside. </p>
<p>One of the most common solutions for hoverboard issues is calibrating your board. Here are the steps involved in hoverboard calibration:</p>
<ol><li>Start with the HOVERFLY hoverboard powered off.</li>
<li>Adjust the foot pedals until they are level with each other and the ground.</li>
<li>Press and hold the power button for 10 seconds. Another beep will sound and the LED lights will flash.</li>
<li>Press the power button to turn off. </li>
<li>Press the power button to turn on. The HOVERFLY hoverboard will be calibrated and ready for galactic adventures.</li>
</ol><p><strong>NOTE:</strong> You may have to repeat the above process multiple times in order to fully reset and calibrate your hoverboard. For example, you may have to go through the process 3 times in a row before the calibration fully takes effect. </p>
<p>Plus, you can also watch the full recalibration process in the video below.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-troubleshoot-hoverboard/">How Do I Troubleshoot My Hoverboard?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Do I Do if My Hoverboard is Not Working?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/hoverboard-not-working/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 23:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Diandra]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=10361</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>It can be very disappointing to discover that your hoverboard is not working. Luckily, GOTRAX hoverboards have a built-in feature [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/hoverboard-not-working/">What Do I Do if My Hoverboard is Not Working?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>It can be very disappointing to discover that your hoverboard is not working. Luckily, GOTRAX hoverboards have a built-in feature that often works as a solution to many different hoverboard issues. </p>
<p>If you ever find that your HOVERFLY is not working then the first thing you should try is calibrating the board which involves 5 easy steps. </p>
<ol><li>Start with the HOVERFLY hoverboard powered off.</li>
<li>Adjust the foot pedals until they are level with each other and the ground.</li>
<li>Press and hold the power button for 10 seconds. Another beep will sound and the LED lights will flash.</li>
<li>Press the power button to turn off. </li>
<li>Press the power button to turn on. The HOVERFLY hoverboard will be calibrated and ready for galactic adventures.</li>
</ol><p><strong>NOTE:</strong> You may have to repeat the above process multiple times in order to fully reset and calibrate your hoverboard. For example, you may have to go through the process 3 times in a row before the recalibration fully takes effect.</p>
<p>We&rsquo;ve also make a handy how-to video that shows you the full process. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/hoverboard-not-working/">What Do I Do if My Hoverboard is Not Working?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Do I Fix My Hoverboard?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/fix-my-hoverboard/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 23:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Diandra]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=10351</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s possible that you may run into certain issues when riding or charging your hoverboard that you need to fix. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/fix-my-hoverboard/">How Do I Fix My Hoverboard?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>It&rsquo;s possible that you may run into certain issues when riding or charging your hoverboard that you need to fix. At GOTRAX, we want our COMMANDERS to have the chance to fully enjoy and have light-years of fun on their HOVERFLY hoverboards. That&rsquo;s why our HOVERFLYs were designed with one simple solution to help fix a variety of different issues called calibration. </p>
<p>Our Mission Support Specialists will often advise COMMANDERS to try calibrating their HOVERFLY hoverboards before making any other, more drastic repairs. Luckily, the process of calibrating your hoverboard is simple and involves only 5 steps. </p>
<ol><li>Start with the HOVERFLY hoverboard powered off.</li>
<li>Adjust the foot pedals until they are level with each other and the ground.</li>
<li>Press and hold the power button for 10 seconds. Another beep will sound and the LED lights will flash.</li>
<li>Press the power button to turn off. </li>
<li>Press the power button to turn on. The HOVERFLY hoverboard will be calibrated and ready for galactic adventures.</li>
</ol><p><strong>NOTE:</strong> You may have to repeat the above process multiple times in order to fully reset and calibrate your hoverboard. For example, you may have to go through the process 3 times in a row before the recalibration fully takes effect.</p>
<p>You can also watch the full calibration process in the handy how-to video below.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/fix-my-hoverboard/">How Do I Fix My Hoverboard?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Recalibrate Your Hoverboard</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-recalibrate-hoverboard/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 23:08:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Diandra]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=10338</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Calibrating your HOVERFLY hoverboard will reset the system and the foot pedals to help fix any self-balancing issues that may [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-recalibrate-hoverboard/">How to Recalibrate Your Hoverboard</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Calibrating your HOVERFLY hoverboard will reset the system and the foot pedals to help fix any self-balancing issues that may develop over time. Some GOTRAX Commanders may even need to recalibrate their hoverboard occasionally. </p>
<p>Luckily, calibrating is an easy and simple solution that can fix a number of issues. Here are all the steps you must complete in order to recalibrate your HOVERFLY hoverboard. </p>
<ol><li>Start with the HOVERFLY hoverboard powered off.</li>
<li>Adjust the foot pedals until they are level with each other and the ground.</li>
<li>Press and hold the power button for 10 seconds. Another beep will sound and the LED lights will flash.</li>
<li>Press the power button to turn off. </li>
<li>Press the power button to turn on. The HOVERFLY hoverboard will be calibrated and ready for galactic adventures.</li>
</ol><p><strong>NOTE:</strong> You may have to repeat the above process multiple times in order to fully reset and calibrate your hoverboard. For example, you may have to go through the process 3 times in a row before the recalibration fully takes effect.</p>
<p>You can also watch the full calibration process in the video below.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-recalibrate-hoverboard/">How to Recalibrate Your Hoverboard</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Calibrate Your Hoverboard</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/calibrate-your-hoverboard/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 22:48:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Diandra]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=10317</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Hoverboards were designed so that many of the most common issues owners face could be solved by calibrating the board. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/calibrate-your-hoverboard/">How to Calibrate Your Hoverboard</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Hoverboards were designed so that many of the most common issues owners face could be solved by calibrating the board. At times, you may need to calibrate your HOVERFLY hoverboard so you can continue to have the best hoverflying experience. Calibrating your HOVERFLY hoverboard will reset the system and foot pedals in order to correct any self-balancing issues that may develop over time or as a result of shifting during traveling.  </p>
<p>Here are the steps involved in calibrating or recalibrating your HOVERFLY hoverboard:</p>
<ol><li>Start with the HOVERFLY hoverboard powered off.</li>
<li>Adjust the foot pedals until they are level with each other and the ground.</li>
<li>Press and hold the power button for 10 seconds. Another beep will sound and the LED lights will flash.</li>
<li>Press the power button to turn off. </li>
<li>Press the power button to turn on. The HOVERFLY hoverboard will be calibrated and ready for galactic adventures.</li>
</ol><p><strong>NOTE:</strong> You may have to repeat the above process multiple times in order to fully reset and calibrate your hoverboard. For example, you may have to go through the process 3 times in a row before the recalibration fully takes effect.</p>
<p>You can also watch the full calibration process in the video below.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/calibrate-your-hoverboard/">How to Calibrate Your Hoverboard</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Fast Are Electric Scooters?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-fast-electric-scooters/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 16:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Diandra]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=9220</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>If you want to experience the thrill of gliding through the GOTRAX GALAXY, you can on a GOTRAX GLIDER electric [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-fast-electric-scooters/">How Fast Are Electric Scooters?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you want to experience the thrill of gliding through the GOTRAX GALAXY, you can on a <a href="https://gotrax.com/shop/electric-scooters/glider/">GOTRAX GLIDER electric scooter</a>. Our fleet of top-class machines travel at up to 17 mph. That&rsquo;s an impressively fast rate of travel for any world be craft commander out there. </p>
<p>Stepping on an electric scooter should be an exciting experience. This is why you want to go as fast as possible while remaining safe. The team of experts at GOTRAX Command know how important the thrill is. This is why they designed each of our awesome looking scooters to be able to travel at a maximum speed of 17 mph. Commanding your own GOTRAX GLIDER is a much better way to get around than walking. </p>
<p>You can zip in and out of people and obstacles, so nothing gets in the way. If you&rsquo;re in a real hurry, and you want to use the power of public transport along the way, that isn&rsquo;t a problem. You can just bring your craft to a halt, fold it up and carry it with you on a bus or train. It&rsquo;s a really simple process and takes just seconds. We know how hectic galactic exploration can be, so we make sure you don&rsquo;t waste any time. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-fast-electric-scooters/">How Fast Are Electric Scooters?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
