<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Products and Parts &#8211; GOTRAX</title>
	<atom:link href="https://gotrax.com/support/faqs/parts/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://gotrax.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 23:30:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	
	<item>
		<title>What is the Return Policy for GOTRAX products?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/return-policy-gotrax/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 17:27:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Diandra]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=8907</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Customer satisfaction is mission critical for the GOTRAX team which is why all our products come a 30-day&#160;no hassles return [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/return-policy-gotrax/">What is the Return Policy for GOTRAX products?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Customer satisfaction is mission critical for the <a href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a> team which is why all our products come a 30-day&nbsp;no hassles return policy.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">GOTRAX only processes returns and refunds for products ordered directly from GOTRAX.com. Citizens wanting to return a product or seeking a refund from an authorized dealer in store or online should consult the original retailer.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Generally, GOTRAX will accept return of new, unused products ordered from the website within 30 calendar days. Items must be sent back in their GOTRAX original packaging and postmarked within 30 days of the original receipt. Give us at least two weeks to process your request. Our Commanders and Mission Support Specialists are the best in the galaxy, but they sometimes still need a bit of time to make sure everything is in order. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Take note, Citizens! As much as your satisfaction is a vital part of the GOTRAX mission, failure to follow instructions could result in delay and affect refund eligibility. Step-by-step instructions can be found in our Return Guidelines at GOTRAX.com/support/gotrax-return-policy.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For returns or refunds from other authorized retailers, whether online or in-store, contact the original seller for more information. </span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/return-policy-gotrax/">What is the Return Policy for GOTRAX products?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Do I Charge the Battery in My GLIDER Electric Scooter?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/charge-battery-electric-scooter/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 19:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Diandra]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=7685</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Following the battery charging instructions below will ensure the safety of you and others and the proper operation of your [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/charge-battery-electric-scooter/">How Do I Charge the Battery in My GLIDER Electric Scooter?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Following the battery charging instructions below will ensure the safety of you and others and the proper operation of your <a href="https://gotrax.com/shop/electric-scooters/glider/">GOTRAX GLIDER Electric Scooter</a>.</p>
<ul><li>After the removal of all packaging, plug the provided charger and adapter into a grounded outlet (100V-240V; 50-60Hz).</li>
<li>Plug the other end of the charger / adapter into the battery charging port of the GOTRAX GLIDER located below the power button towards the top of<br>
the handlebars behind a black rubber cover. The indicator light will turn to red to confirm that the product is charging.</li>
<li>The GLIDER battery will take approximately 3 hours to fully charge.</li>
<li>The GLIDER battery is fully charged when the indicator light changes from red to green.</li>
<li>Detach the charger / adapter from the GOTRAX GLIDER before turning on or operating.</li>
</ul><p>Always adhere to the safety warnings in the GOTRAX GLIDER Commander&rsquo;s Manual when charging your battery.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/charge-battery-electric-scooter/">How Do I Charge the Battery in My GLIDER Electric Scooter?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Who do I contact if I have questions about my GOTRAX order from Amazon.com?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/questions-order-amazon/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 16:53:56 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[hkskewes@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=1695</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>GOTRAX wants to ensure satisfaction for its Citizens regardless of where they order our products. This includes customers who purchase [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/questions-order-amazon/">Who do I contact if I have questions about my GOTRAX order from Amazon.com?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">GOTRAX wants to ensure satisfaction for its Citizens regardless of where they order <a href="https://gotrax.com/">our products</a>. This includes customers who purchase from Amazon.</span></p>
<p>No matter where you purchase your GOTRAX rideable, all Commanders are encouraged to <a href="https://gotrax.com/support/warranty-registration/">register the warranty</a> on their product. And if you have any questions or issues with your rideable, you can reach out to our Mission Support Specialists with <a href="https://gotrax.com/support/contact-us/">the information on this contact page</a>. </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">For general Amazon questions, you can call Amazon&rsquo;s customer support number at (888) 280-4331. You can also head over to the </span><a href="https://www.amazon.com/sp?_encoding=UTF8&amp;asin=&amp;isAmazonFulfilled=&amp;isCBA=&amp;marketplaceID=ATVPDKIKX0DER&amp;orderID=&amp;seller=ANR9XBZ54OC79&amp;tab=&amp;vasStoreID="><span style="font-weight: 400">GOTRAX Amazon storefront</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> and click &ldquo;Ask a Question&rdquo; on the right side of the page. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Amazon also has a </span><a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/?nodeId=201331410"><span style="font-weight: 400">handy list of helpful topics</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">&nbsp;for customers ranging from finding a missing package to tracking a shipment. </span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/questions-order-amazon/">Who do I contact if I have questions about my GOTRAX order from Amazon.com?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What&#8217;s inside a self-balancing scooter?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/inside-self-balancing-scooter/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 17:37:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Diandra]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=3014</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking inside a self-balancing scooter is a great way to see how far technology has come. Human technology used to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/inside-self-balancing-scooter/">What&#8217;s inside a self-balancing scooter?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking inside a self-balancing scooter is a great way to see how far technology has come. Human technology used to be slow, clunky and powered by steam.</p>
<p>Now, we have miniature batteries and computers in everything, making our lives so much more comfortable. Something like hoverboards would be impossible a mere 100 years ago, but now any Earthling can buy their very own GOTRAX HOVERFLY.</p>
<p>There&rsquo;s so much going on in a hoverboard that you wouldn&rsquo;t believe it unless you saw it with your own eyes. So, now we&rsquo;re going to take a peek inside a hoverboard and explain what&rsquo;s there. If you&rsquo;re the kind of inquisitive person who enjoys taking things apart, you&rsquo;ll like this look at what&rsquo;s inside a self-balancing scooter.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/inside-self-balancing-scooter/">What&#8217;s inside a self-balancing scooter?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Can a Hoverboard go in snow?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/can-hoverboard-go-snow/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 22:53:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Vasanth]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=2826</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>You know, we don&#8217;t get that much snow on this side of the Milky Way. But from what we understand [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/can-hoverboard-go-snow/">Can a Hoverboard go in snow?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>You know, we don&rsquo;t get that much snow on this side of the Milky Way. But from what we understand about the general physics on Earth, snow is a solid version of rain. So the answer is a resounding no.</p>
<p>Since snow is classified as wet weather, we recommend you leave the hoverboard at home base in the winter. GOTRAX self-balancing scooters are only <strong>designed only for dry weather</strong>. Operating and riding <a href="https://gotrax.com/product/hoverboards/">HOVERFLY hoverboards</a> in the rain or on wet ground can increase the risk of injury due to falling off or losing control. It can also risk damaging the battery.</p>
<p>Check out the Safe Riding Guidelines in the Commander&rsquo;s Manual for more information on how to protect yourself and your board while orbiting around the neighborhood.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/can-hoverboard-go-snow/">Can a Hoverboard go in snow?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How do I dispose of a hoverboard properly?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/dispose-hoverboard-properly/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 23:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[hkskewes@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=2645</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>So, you&#8217;re looking to upgrade your hoverboard after your last one lived its best life? We&#8217;ve got you, Commander! The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/dispose-hoverboard-properly/">How do I dispose of a hoverboard properly?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>So, you&rsquo;re looking to upgrade your hoverboard after your last one lived its best life?</div>
<div></div>
<div>We&rsquo;ve got you, Commander! The GOTRAX team always urges its Citizens to properly dispose of outdated electronics that are no longer useful. Here are some helpful tips on <a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/recycling/how-to-recycle-electronics/">how to get rid of your old electronics in general</a>. We also strongly recommend contacting<span class="author-wetWTeKYkV4c">&nbsp;your local or regional waste management service for&nbsp;information on proper disposal of old electronics and batteries.&nbsp;</span></div>
<div></div>
<div>After that, make sure to head back to GOTRAX to pick up your next hoverboard! Also, check out our other electric rideables so you and yours can get back to cruising the cosmos as soon as possible.</div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/dispose-hoverboard-properly/">How do I dispose of a hoverboard properly?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What kind of battery does GOTRAX use for its hoverboards?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/battery-gotrax-hoverboards/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 16:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[hkskewes@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=2343</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>How do I charge my HOVERFLY? When is it fully charged? The GOTRAX Command Center uses space-age technology to power [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/battery-gotrax-hoverboards/">What kind of battery does GOTRAX use for its hoverboards?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2>How do I charge my HOVERFLY? When is it fully charged?</h2>
<p>The GOTRAX Command Center uses space-age technology to power its hoverboards! We provide all the equipment you need to cruise the cosmos, including battery and charger.</p>
<p>The GOTRAX HOVERFLY and HOVERFLY PLUS use lithium ion batteries both for its power and because it can be recharged. All GOTRAX products with lithium ion batteries are safety-tested and certified under UL 2272.</p>
<p>Only use the charging cable provided to charge your hoverboard! Once you plug it in, a red light on the box located along the charging cable will let you know it&rsquo;s charging, which should only take about an hour. Never leave it plugged in for longer than that. The light will turn green once it&rsquo;s fully charged.</p>
<p>You&rsquo;ll also see a yellow light on the hoverboard itself when you connect it to the charger. That light simply means the hoverboard is connected to the charger.</p>
<p>With a full battery, you can cosmic fun glide for miles before returning to the Space Station to recharge!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/battery-gotrax-hoverboards/">What kind of battery does GOTRAX use for its hoverboards?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What are the differences between the HOVERFLY hoverboards?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/differences-hoverfly-hoverboards/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 23:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=1420</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The flight engineers at GOTRAX recognize that different people have different needs.&#160; What works for one person may not work [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/differences-hoverfly-hoverboards/">What are the differences between the HOVERFLY hoverboards?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">The flight engineers at GOTRAX recognize that different people have different needs.<span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp; </span>What works for one person may not work for others.<span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp; </span>And so they&rsquo;ve developed different HOVERFLY hoverboards to meet those different needs.</span></p>
<p>The <a href="https://gotrax.com/shop/hoverboards/hoverfly/">GOTRAX HOVERFLY</a> is a two-wheel self-balancing scooter aka hoverboard. This self-balancing scooter features two riding modes, battery light indicators, system light indicators, and safety features including non-slip foot platforms and Auto Shutdown.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://gotrax.com/shop/hoverboards/hoverfly-eco/">GOTRAX HOVERFLY ECO</a> is our most affordable two-wheel self-balancing scooter aka hoverboard. This self-balancing scooter features two riding modes, battery light indicators, system light indicators, and safety features including non-slip foot platforms and Auto Shutdown.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://gotrax.com/shop/hoverboards/hoverfly-plus/">HOVERFLY PLUS</a> is a variation of the HOVERFLY self-balancing scooter that has everything that the HOVERFLY features plus a Bluetooth speaker and mobile app with a third riding mode &ndash; the Pro Riding Mode, which is for advanced riders only.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://gotrax.com/shop/hoverboards/hoverfly-xl/">HOVERFLY XL</a> is a variation of the HOVERFLY PLUS self-balancing scooter that has everything that the HOVERFLY PLUS features but with 8-inch tires for all-terrain riding. Like the HOVERFLY PLUS, the HOVERFLY XL boasts a Bluetooth speaker and mobile app with an extra Pro Riding Mode.</p>
<p>Light-years of fun await! Enter the GOTRAX GALAXY now, and <a href="https://gotrax.com/product/hoverboards/">shop our HOVERFLY hoverboards</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/differences-hoverfly-hoverboards/">What are the differences between the HOVERFLY hoverboards?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What do I do if my GOTRAX product came without a cable, power adapter or charger?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/missing-power-adapter-charger/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 00:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[The Firm Web]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://tfghoverfly.wpengine.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=428</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>If your GOTRAX e-rideable came without a cable, power adapter, or charger, simply contact support by calling 1-844-4GOTRAX, or use [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/missing-power-adapter-charger/">What do I do if my GOTRAX product came without a cable, power adapter or charger?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If your <a href="https://gotrax.com/">GOTRAX</a> e-rideable came without a cable, power adapter, or charger, simply contact support by calling 1-844-4GOTRAX, or use the chat option found in the bottom right-hand corner of any page on our website.  Misson Control will get your name and address and get the part out to you right away. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/missing-power-adapter-charger/">What do I do if my GOTRAX product came without a cable, power adapter or charger?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Can I bring my hoverboard on an airplane?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/hoverboard-airplane/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 00:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[The Firm Web]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://tfghoverfly.wpengine.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=427</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Before you try to bring you hoverboard on an airplane, let us give you the lowdown on this! All GOTRAX [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/hoverboard-airplane/">Can I bring my hoverboard on an airplane?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Before you try to bring you hoverboard on an airplane, let us give you the lowdown on this!</p>
<p><a href="https://gotrax.com/">All GOTRAX rideables</a>&nbsp;are prohibited in checked baggage when traveling by plane due to their batteries. After all, with top-ranking torque comes a powerful battery.</p>
<p>The&nbsp;Federal Aviation Administration Office of Hazardous Materials Safety recommends that passengers get permission from the individual airline for devices that contain lithium-ion batteries that have a higher watt-hour than say a cell phone, tablet, tool, camera, PDA, or laptop would have. The GOTRAX products will likely fall in this category. The FAA bases these guidelines on US DOT regulations.</p>
<p>To find more information on these guidelines head over <a href="https://www.faa.gov/about/office_org/headquarters_offices/ash/ash_programs/hazmat/passenger_info/media/airline_passengers_and_batteries.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.faa.gov</a>.</p>
<p>The FAA also advises that the TSA security, as well as individual airlines and international rules, can sometimes&nbsp;be tougher when it comes to these sorts of things.</p>
<p>We know you love your <a href="https://gotrax.com/shop/hoverboards/hoverfly/">HOVERFLY Hoverboard</a> and want to show your&nbsp;friends, cousins, and first cousins twice removed, but we say skip the potential hassle and leave your prized GOTRAX product at home. This way, you can prevent any potential headaches that may result from trying to take your hoverboard on an airplane. You don&rsquo;t want to miss your flight because you have to run your HOVERFLY Hoverboard or GLIDER Electric Scooter back to your home base.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/hoverboard-airplane/">Can I bring my hoverboard on an airplane?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
