<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Amazon Orders &#8211; GOTRAX</title>
	<atom:link href="https://gotrax.com/support/faqs/amazon-orders/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://gotrax.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 23:30:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	
	<item>
		<title>Who do I contact if I have questions about my GOTRAX order from Amazon.com?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/questions-order-amazon/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 16:53:56 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[hkskewes@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=1695</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>GOTRAX wants to ensure satisfaction for its Citizens regardless of where they order our products. This includes customers who purchase [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/questions-order-amazon/">Who do I contact if I have questions about my GOTRAX order from Amazon.com?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">GOTRAX wants to ensure satisfaction for its Citizens regardless of where they order <a href="https://gotrax.com/">our products</a>. This includes customers who purchase from Amazon.</span></p>
<p>No matter where you purchase your GOTRAX rideable, all Commanders are encouraged to <a href="https://gotrax.com/support/warranty-registration/">register the warranty</a> on their product. And if you have any questions or issues with your rideable, you can reach out to our Mission Support Specialists with <a href="https://gotrax.com/support/contact-us/">the information on this contact page</a>. </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">For general Amazon questions, you can call Amazon&rsquo;s customer support number at (888) 280-4331. You can also head over to the </span><a href="https://www.amazon.com/sp?_encoding=UTF8&amp;asin=&amp;isAmazonFulfilled=&amp;isCBA=&amp;marketplaceID=ATVPDKIKX0DER&amp;orderID=&amp;seller=ANR9XBZ54OC79&amp;tab=&amp;vasStoreID="><span style="font-weight: 400">GOTRAX Amazon storefront</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> and click &ldquo;Ask a Question&rdquo; on the right side of the page. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Amazon also has a </span><a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/?nodeId=201331410"><span style="font-weight: 400">handy list of helpful topics</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">&nbsp;for customers ranging from finding a missing package to tracking a shipment. </span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/questions-order-amazon/">Who do I contact if I have questions about my GOTRAX order from Amazon.com?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I bought my GOTRAX electric rideable on Amazon. What is the return policy?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/amazon-return-policy</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 20:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[hkskewes@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=1703</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Amazon is one of GOTRAX&#8217;s partners in space flight and customer satisfaction! In most cases, Amazon&#8217;s Return Policy allows customers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/amazon-return-policy">I bought my GOTRAX electric rideable on Amazon. What is the return policy?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Amazon is one of GOTRAX&rsquo;s partners in space flight and customer satisfaction!</p>
<p>In most cases, Amazon&rsquo;s Return Policy allows customers to return items within 30 days of shipment receipt. If your GOTRAX product is not eligible for a return or a refund, you can also sell it on Amazon.com yourself or trade it in for an Amazon Gift Card.</p>
<p>If you decide to sell yourself, there is no listing fee for individual sellers, and you can set your own price. For a trade-in, customers get an immediate offer and can ship the item for free.</p>
<p>To set up a return on Amazon, head over to the <a href="http://amazon.com/gp/orc/returns/homepage.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Returns Center</a> and follow the step-by-step instructions they provide. In general, you&rsquo;ll need to get your package ready, pack items securely, and make sure you have all your paperwork to send it back.</p>
<p>If you don&rsquo;t have the original packaging, just use a sturdy box and pad the item with something like newspaper or bubble wrap when packing your item. After it&rsquo;s all packed and ready to go, attach the return label to the outside of the box and follow the instructions based on the return shipping method you selected.</p>
<p>If you are returning a gift, you&rsquo;ll need to select the &ldquo;Return a Gift&rdquo; option at the Returns Center and sign in with your Amazon account.</p>
<p>You&rsquo;ll also need to find the gift&rsquo;s order number on the left side of the packing slip that came with your gift. If you don&rsquo;t have a packing slip, you can contact Amazon&rsquo;s customer support at 1 (888) 280-4331 to help you.</p>
<p>Be ready with information like the sender&rsquo;s name, the shipping address, the email address or the phone number attached to the order. After that you&rsquo;ll be able to follow the steps below:</p>
<ul><li>Enter the gift&rsquo;s order number and hit &ldquo;Search.&rdquo;</li>
<li>Select the items from the order you want to send back.</li>
<li>Enter the quantity of each item and the reason for the return.</li>
<li>Pick the return shipping method you want and how you want to access the return label, which is assigned to specific returns.</li>
<li>Include the return authorization from Amazon inside the package you&rsquo;re sending back and attach the label to the outside of the package.</li>
</ul><p>If the gift return is authorized, either Amazon or the original seller will process the refund as an Amazon.com Gift Card after the return is received. The Amazon Gift Card will be added to the account used to request the return. Amazon will send a confirmation email once the refund is processed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/amazon-return-policy">I bought my GOTRAX electric rideable on Amazon. What is the return policy?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How do I track my GOTRAX order from Amazon.com?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/track-gotrax-order-amazon</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 23:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[hkskewes@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=1705</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>With space-age technology, Citizens can track their GOTRAX order from Amazon as it makes its way across the galaxy! To [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/track-gotrax-order-amazon">How do I track my GOTRAX order from Amazon.com?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With space-age technology, Citizens can track their GOTRAX order from Amazon as it makes its way across the galaxy!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To track your Amazon.com order, log in to your account, go to &ldquo;</span><a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/css/your-orders-access" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Your Orders</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">,&rdquo; go to the specific order you want to track and click &ldquo;Track Package.&rdquo; If the tracking information is missing, Amazon has a helpful list of reasons why that might be. You can find it </span><a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=200348190" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">here</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If the tracking information on Amazon does not match the carrier&rsquo;s website, it is fairly common for Amazon customers to see slight differences. Every carrier has its own alien language to communicate shipment updates, and Amazon translates those updates, so it&rsquo;s easier to understand. You can find more information on differences in tracking information </span><a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=201118210" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">here</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/track-gotrax-order-amazon">How do I track my GOTRAX order from Amazon.com?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Does the GOTRAX warranty still apply if I bought my electric rideable on Amazon?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/gotrax-warranty-amazon-orders</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 23:43:21 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[hkskewes@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=1702</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Absolutely! The GOTRAX team stands behind all vehicles in its fleet regardless of where you purchased it. But you will [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/gotrax-warranty-amazon-orders">Does the GOTRAX warranty still apply if I bought my electric rideable on Amazon?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Absolutely! The GOTRAX team stands behind all vehicles in its fleet regardless of where you purchased it. But you will still need to register your electric rideable with GOTRAX within 30 days of purchase for coverage under the 90-Day Limited Warranty we offer. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Head over to </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://gotrax.com/warranty" target="_blank" rel="noopener">GOTRAX.com/warranty</a> to register GOTRAX product for warranty. You&rsquo;ll need: </span></p>
<ul><li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Name of the Point of Purchase</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Date Purchased</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Invoice/Receipt/Order Number</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Model Number</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Serial Number</span></li>
</ul><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For more information about the warranty, visit <a href="https://gotrax.com/warranty" target="_blank" rel="noopener">GOTRAX.com/warranty</a>.</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/gotrax-warranty-amazon-orders">Does the GOTRAX warranty still apply if I bought my electric rideable on Amazon?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Are sleeves or skins available for GOTRAX HOVERFLY hoverboards?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/sleeves-skins-for-gotrax-hoverboards/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 23:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[hkskewes@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=2264</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Fear not, Commander! While we don&#8217;t currently have our own hoverboard skins or sleeves available on our website, the GOTRAX [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/sleeves-skins-for-gotrax-hoverboards/">Are sleeves or skins available for GOTRAX HOVERFLY hoverboards?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Fear not, Commander! While we don&rsquo;t currently have our own hoverboard skins or sleeves available on our website, the GOTRAX HOVERFLY Hoverboard works with most all sleeves and skins that are available elsewhere for purchase.</p>
<p>Just look for skins or sleeves that fit hoverboards with 6.5-inch wheels, and you shouldn&rsquo;t have any problems finding the right fit.</p>
<p>This is just another reason why the GOTRAX HOVERFLY hoverboard was voted one of the best hoverboards under $250!</p>
<p>We&rsquo;re on a mission to optimize the cosmic fun factor of the GOTRAX HOVERFLY Hoverboard self-balancing scooter. Stay tuned for the launch announcement of our GOTRAX HOVERFLY Hoverboard custom-designed skins coming soon.</p>
<p>To make sure you&rsquo;re getting updates,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.facebook.com/RideGOTRAX/">follow GOTRAX on Facebook</a> and sign up with your email on our website for $10 off your first purchase!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/sleeves-skins-for-gotrax-hoverboards/">Are sleeves or skins available for GOTRAX HOVERFLY hoverboards?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
