<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Hoverboards &#8211; GOTRAX</title>
	<atom:link href="https://gotrax.com/support/faqs/hoverboards/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://gotrax.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 23:30:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	
	<item>
		<title>How Do Hoverboards Work and Function?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-do-hoverboards-work/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 20:23:45 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeff Lawrence]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=13402</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>From the outside, it looks like hoverboards work in mysterious ways, but the truth is these cosmically fun e-rideables are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-do-hoverboards-work/">How Do Hoverboards Work and Function?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>From the outside, it looks like hoverboards work in mysterious ways, but the truth is these cosmically fun e-rideables are built with space-age technology and we&rsquo;ll tell you exactly how a <a href="https://gotrax.com/product/hoverboards/">hoverboard</a> works. The GOTRAX HOVERFLY XL and HOVERFLY ECO self-balancing scooters use electric motors, self-balancing technology, and sensors to detect speed and tilt. Combined, these allow riders to easily stand up, accelerate, turn, and stop simply by shifting your weight.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-do-hoverboards-work/">How Do Hoverboards Work and Function?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is there a Hoverboard store near me?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/hoverboard-store-information/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 23:49:32 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeff Lawrence]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=13128</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Where to find a hoverboard store Many people want to physically hold a product in their hands before they actually [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/hoverboard-store-information/">Is there a Hoverboard store near me?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2>Where to find a hoverboard store</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Many people want to physically hold a product in their hands before they actually make a purchase. &nbsp;This makes sense a lot of the time. &nbsp;&nbsp;Some people really need that tactile experience before they buy the product. &nbsp;If you&rsquo;re one of those people, you&rsquo;ll be happy to know that our hoverboards can be found at Walmart, as well as Dunham&rsquo;s Sports. However most hoverboards are sold at a &nbsp;online hoverboard store, luckily we do our best to show cover all the features and specifications so that you can make the best choice before deciding on a hoverboard.</span></p>
<h2>Why Choose a Gotrax Hoverboard?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Our <a href="https://gotrax.com/product/hoverboards/">hoverboards</a> are of course a great choice. &nbsp;The Gotrax XL off road hoverboard offers powerful dual 350W motors, capable of reaching 7.4 mph. The advanced lithium ion batteries give our Hoverfly an impressive range of up to 12 miles. &nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It&rsquo;s also one of the safest boards on the market. &nbsp;It features an advanced gyroscopic balance system. &nbsp;This is of course a little different from how most vehicles are operated, and can take some getting used to. &nbsp;That&rsquo;s why our boards come standard with a training mode. &nbsp;This mode reduces the maximum speed of the board, minimizing the negative effects of any balance mistakes made while learning. &nbsp;The board also features bright LED headlights, and antislip foot grips, to further increase safety. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The board is also constructed to the highest standards. &nbsp;All electrical components are tested and certified to UL 2272 standards. &nbsp;This makes them some of the safest most dependable components out there.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/hoverboard-store-information/">Is there a Hoverboard store near me?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is a Balancing Electric Scooter?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/what-balancing-electric-scooter/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 21:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Diandra]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=11363</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A balancing electric scooter, self-balancing scooter, or hoverboard, is a two-wheeled electric rideable. They consist of motorized wheels, connected to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/what-balancing-electric-scooter/">What is a Balancing Electric Scooter?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A balancing electric scooter, self-balancing scooter, or <a href="https://gotrax.com/product/hoverboards/">hoverboard</a>, is a two-wheeled electric rideable.  They consist of motorized wheels, connected to a pair of articulating pods.  You can travel forwards or backward by leaning, and steering is controlled by the pods.  </p>
<p>Balancing electric scooters are great for personal transportation and recreation.  Different models come with different features that allow them to be used in different types of terrain, including off-road. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/what-balancing-electric-scooter/">What is a Balancing Electric Scooter?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Do I Charge the Battery in my HOVERFLY Hoverboard?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/charge-battery-hoverfly-hoverboard/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 18:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Diandra]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=10684</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Before charging your HOVERFLY hoverboard, please carefully adhere to all instructions and safety warnings in the Commander&#8217;s Manual to minimize [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/charge-battery-hoverfly-hoverboard/">How Do I Charge the Battery in my HOVERFLY Hoverboard?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Before charging your HOVERFLY hoverboard, please carefully adhere to all instructions and safety warnings in the <a href="https://gotrax.com/usermanuals">Commander&rsquo;s Manual</a> to minimize the risk of personal injury or property damage.</p>
<p>Following the charging instructions will ensure the safety of you and others and the proper operation of your GOTRAX hoverboard.</p>
<ol><li>After removing all packaging, plug the provided charger/adapter into a grounded outlet (100V-240V; 50-60Hz).</li>
<li>Plug the other end of the charger/adapter into the battery charging port of the GOTRAX HOVERFLY located on the back left side of the unit. The indicator light on the charger/adapter will turn to red to confirm that the product is charging.</li>
<li>The GOTRAX HOVERFLY battery will take approximately 1 hour to fully charge.</li>
<li>The GOTRAX HOVERFLY battery is fully charged when the indicator light on the charger/adapter changes from red to green.</li>
<li>Detach the charger/adapter from the GOTRAX HOVERFLY before turning on or operating.</li>
</ol>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/charge-battery-hoverfly-hoverboard/">How Do I Charge the Battery in my HOVERFLY Hoverboard?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Do I Troubleshoot My Hoverboard?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-troubleshoot-hoverboard/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 00:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Diandra]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=10363</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The first step for troubleshooting issues with your hoverboard is to check the Commander&#8217;s Manual. You can find the manual [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-troubleshoot-hoverboard/">How Do I Troubleshoot My Hoverboard?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The first step for troubleshooting issues with your hoverboard is to check the Commander&rsquo;s Manual. You can find the manual for your HOVERFLY model on this page. And it&rsquo;s very likely that the information you need to troubleshoot will be inside. </p>
<p>One of the most common solutions for hoverboard issues is calibrating your board. Here are the steps involved in hoverboard calibration:</p>
<ol><li>Start with the HOVERFLY hoverboard powered off.</li>
<li>Adjust the foot pedals until they are level with each other and the ground.</li>
<li>Press and hold the power button for 10 seconds. Another beep will sound and the LED lights will flash.</li>
<li>Press the power button to turn off. </li>
<li>Press the power button to turn on. The HOVERFLY hoverboard will be calibrated and ready for galactic adventures.</li>
</ol><p><strong>NOTE:</strong> You may have to repeat the above process multiple times in order to fully reset and calibrate your hoverboard. For example, you may have to go through the process 3 times in a row before the calibration fully takes effect. </p>
<p>Plus, you can also watch the full recalibration process in the video below.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-troubleshoot-hoverboard/">How Do I Troubleshoot My Hoverboard?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Do I Do if My Hoverboard is Not Working?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/hoverboard-not-working/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 23:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Diandra]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=10361</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>It can be very disappointing to discover that your hoverboard is not working. Luckily, GOTRAX hoverboards have a built-in feature [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/hoverboard-not-working/">What Do I Do if My Hoverboard is Not Working?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>It can be very disappointing to discover that your hoverboard is not working. Luckily, GOTRAX hoverboards have a built-in feature that often works as a solution to many different hoverboard issues. </p>
<p>If you ever find that your HOVERFLY is not working then the first thing you should try is calibrating the board which involves 5 easy steps. </p>
<ol><li>Start with the HOVERFLY hoverboard powered off.</li>
<li>Adjust the foot pedals until they are level with each other and the ground.</li>
<li>Press and hold the power button for 10 seconds. Another beep will sound and the LED lights will flash.</li>
<li>Press the power button to turn off. </li>
<li>Press the power button to turn on. The HOVERFLY hoverboard will be calibrated and ready for galactic adventures.</li>
</ol><p><strong>NOTE:</strong> You may have to repeat the above process multiple times in order to fully reset and calibrate your hoverboard. For example, you may have to go through the process 3 times in a row before the recalibration fully takes effect.</p>
<p>We&rsquo;ve also make a handy how-to video that shows you the full process. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/hoverboard-not-working/">What Do I Do if My Hoverboard is Not Working?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Do I Fix My Hoverboard?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/fix-my-hoverboard/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 23:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Diandra]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=10351</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s possible that you may run into certain issues when riding or charging your hoverboard that you need to fix. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/fix-my-hoverboard/">How Do I Fix My Hoverboard?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>It&rsquo;s possible that you may run into certain issues when riding or charging your hoverboard that you need to fix. At GOTRAX, we want our COMMANDERS to have the chance to fully enjoy and have light-years of fun on their HOVERFLY hoverboards. That&rsquo;s why our HOVERFLYs were designed with one simple solution to help fix a variety of different issues called calibration. </p>
<p>Our Mission Support Specialists will often advise COMMANDERS to try calibrating their HOVERFLY hoverboards before making any other, more drastic repairs. Luckily, the process of calibrating your hoverboard is simple and involves only 5 steps. </p>
<ol><li>Start with the HOVERFLY hoverboard powered off.</li>
<li>Adjust the foot pedals until they are level with each other and the ground.</li>
<li>Press and hold the power button for 10 seconds. Another beep will sound and the LED lights will flash.</li>
<li>Press the power button to turn off. </li>
<li>Press the power button to turn on. The HOVERFLY hoverboard will be calibrated and ready for galactic adventures.</li>
</ol><p><strong>NOTE:</strong> You may have to repeat the above process multiple times in order to fully reset and calibrate your hoverboard. For example, you may have to go through the process 3 times in a row before the recalibration fully takes effect.</p>
<p>You can also watch the full calibration process in the handy how-to video below.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/fix-my-hoverboard/">How Do I Fix My Hoverboard?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Recalibrate Your Hoverboard</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-recalibrate-hoverboard/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 23:08:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Diandra]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=10338</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Calibrating your HOVERFLY hoverboard will reset the system and the foot pedals to help fix any self-balancing issues that may [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-recalibrate-hoverboard/">How to Recalibrate Your Hoverboard</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Calibrating your HOVERFLY hoverboard will reset the system and the foot pedals to help fix any self-balancing issues that may develop over time. Some GOTRAX Commanders may even need to recalibrate their hoverboard occasionally. </p>
<p>Luckily, calibrating is an easy and simple solution that can fix a number of issues. Here are all the steps you must complete in order to recalibrate your HOVERFLY hoverboard. </p>
<ol><li>Start with the HOVERFLY hoverboard powered off.</li>
<li>Adjust the foot pedals until they are level with each other and the ground.</li>
<li>Press and hold the power button for 10 seconds. Another beep will sound and the LED lights will flash.</li>
<li>Press the power button to turn off. </li>
<li>Press the power button to turn on. The HOVERFLY hoverboard will be calibrated and ready for galactic adventures.</li>
</ol><p><strong>NOTE:</strong> You may have to repeat the above process multiple times in order to fully reset and calibrate your hoverboard. For example, you may have to go through the process 3 times in a row before the recalibration fully takes effect.</p>
<p>You can also watch the full calibration process in the video below.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-recalibrate-hoverboard/">How to Recalibrate Your Hoverboard</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Calibrate Your Hoverboard</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/calibrate-your-hoverboard/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 22:48:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Diandra]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=10317</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Hoverboards were designed so that many of the most common issues owners face could be solved by calibrating the board. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/calibrate-your-hoverboard/">How to Calibrate Your Hoverboard</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Hoverboards were designed so that many of the most common issues owners face could be solved by calibrating the board. At times, you may need to calibrate your HOVERFLY hoverboard so you can continue to have the best hoverflying experience. Calibrating your HOVERFLY hoverboard will reset the system and foot pedals in order to correct any self-balancing issues that may develop over time or as a result of shifting during traveling.  </p>
<p>Here are the steps involved in calibrating or recalibrating your HOVERFLY hoverboard:</p>
<ol><li>Start with the HOVERFLY hoverboard powered off.</li>
<li>Adjust the foot pedals until they are level with each other and the ground.</li>
<li>Press and hold the power button for 10 seconds. Another beep will sound and the LED lights will flash.</li>
<li>Press the power button to turn off. </li>
<li>Press the power button to turn on. The HOVERFLY hoverboard will be calibrated and ready for galactic adventures.</li>
</ol><p><strong>NOTE:</strong> You may have to repeat the above process multiple times in order to fully reset and calibrate your hoverboard. For example, you may have to go through the process 3 times in a row before the recalibration fully takes effect.</p>
<p>You can also watch the full calibration process in the video below.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/calibrate-your-hoverboard/">How to Calibrate Your Hoverboard</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Are There Stores that Sell Hoverboards?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/stores-sell-hoverboards/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 16:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Diandra]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=6792</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>So you just can&#8217;t wait to lay your hands on a GOTRAX HOVERFLY, HOVERFLY PLUS, HOVERFLY XL or a HOVERFLY [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/stores-sell-hoverboards/">Are There Stores that Sell Hoverboards?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>So you just can&rsquo;t wait to lay your hands on a <a href="https://gotrax.com/product/hoverboards/">GOTRAX HOVERFLY, HOVERFLY PLUS, HOVERFLY XL or a HOVERFLY ECO</a>, which means you need to find stores that sell hoverboards. </p>
<p>GOTRAX rideables can be found at trusted retailers like Walmart, <a href="https://www.amazon.com/GOTRAX-Hoverfly-ECO-Hover-board/dp/B076CK8TLH/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;sr=8-2-fkmr1&amp;keywords=hover+board">Amazon.com</a>, and Dunham&rsquo;s Sports.</p>
<p>But the very best place to purchase GOTRAX HOVERFLY Hoverboards is directly from <a href="https://gotrax.com/product/hoverboards/">GOTRAX.com</a>. </p>
<p>Not only does GOTRAX.com have the latest deals on electric rideables, you can also get free shipping on all hoverboards!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/stores-sell-hoverboards/">Are There Stores that Sell Hoverboards?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
