<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Electric Scooters &#8211; GOTRAX</title>
	<atom:link href="https://gotrax.com/support/faqs/electric-scooters/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://gotrax.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 23:30:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	
	<item>
		<title>Can you park an Electric Scooter on the sidewalk?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/electric-scooter-laws-sidewalks/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 17:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeff Lawrence]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=13374</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>So you finally got your hands on one of those ultra cool&#8212;not to mention revolutionary&#8211;GLIDER Electric Scooter. &#160;And even as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/electric-scooter-laws-sidewalks/">Can you park an Electric Scooter on the sidewalk?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So you finally got your hands on one of those ultra cool&mdash;not to mention revolutionary&ndash;GLIDER <a href="https://gotrax.com/shop/electric-scooters/glider/">Electric Scooter</a>. &nbsp;And even as you can&rsquo;t wait to take the ride of a lifetime on this space age transportation toy, wondering as to where in this vast and immense universe you plan to glide&mdash;and glide in style, mind you&mdash;it seems that another, equally important question plagues your mind.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Just where in the blazes can you park the thing? And on a related note, can you park an electric scooter on the sidewalk? Electric Scooter laws can be hard to find and research, and even change from state to state!&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/electric-scooter-laws-sidewalks/">Can you park an Electric Scooter on the sidewalk?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is the Best Electric Scooter for Kids?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/what-is-the-best-electric-scooter-for-kids/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 00:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeff Lawrence]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=13358</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Which is the best electric scooter for kids is of course a fairly complicated question. &#160;There are a whole lot [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/what-is-the-best-electric-scooter-for-kids/">What is the Best Electric Scooter for Kids?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Which is the best <a href="https://gotrax.com/shop/electric-scooters/glider-cadet-electric-scooter-for-kids/">electric scooter for kids</a> is of course a fairly complicated question. &nbsp;There are a whole lot of considerations that come into play, that will be different from person to person. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Naturally, we think ours is a pretty good choice for most people. &nbsp;It combines solid design, great safety features, affordable price, and incredible durability, making it a good choice for most people. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Which is best with anything is of course almost always an issue of contention. &nbsp;Everyone has different needs, and sometimes variables are hard to measure. &nbsp;However here at Gotrax, we believe our Glider Cadet is one of, if not the, best scooter for children on the market. &nbsp;Allow me to elaborate. </span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/what-is-the-best-electric-scooter-for-kids/">What is the Best Electric Scooter for Kids?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What size are the GLIDER Electric Scooter tires?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/size-glider-electric-scooter-tires/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 16:10:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=13164</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Swift, smooth and easy-to-use, the GOTRAX GLIDER Electric Scooter was designed to make commuting fun! Powered by a 250W electric [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/size-glider-electric-scooter-tires/">What size are the GLIDER Electric Scooter tires?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Swift, smooth and easy-to-use, the GOTRAX GLIDER Electric Scooter was designed to make commuting fun!</p>
<p>Powered by a 250W electric motor, this scooter can glide up to 17 mph for up to 9 miles on a single charge.</p>
<p>You can count on a smooth ride every time, thanks to the GLIDER&rsquo;s <strong>5.5-inch front tire and 5-inch back tire</strong>.</p>
<p>The GLIDER comes in three colors straight from the cosmos: Nebula Black, Mars Red and Pulsar Pink.</p>
<p>Learn more about the GLIDER <a href="https://gotrax.com/shop/electric-scooters/glider/">Electric Scooter</a> from GOTRAX and experience the cosmic fun gliding for yourself!</p>
<p>For more information on our scooters check out our guide to finding the <a href="https://gotrax.com/news/best-electric-scooter-reviews/">best electric scooter</a> for you!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/size-glider-electric-scooter-tires/">What size are the GLIDER Electric Scooter tires?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Can Electric Scooters Go Long Distances?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-far-can-electric-scooters-go</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2018 00:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cambria Olsen]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=12599</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>You can&#8217;t wait to get going on your shiny new GOTRAX GLIDER Electric Scooter, a revolutionary interplanetary vehicle that Glides [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-far-can-electric-scooters-go">Can Electric Scooters Go Long Distances?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You can&rsquo;t wait to get going on your shiny new GOTRAX GLIDER <a href="https://gotrax.com/product/electric-scooters/">Electric Scooter</a>, a revolutionary interplanetary vehicle that Glides along at speeds up to 17 mph with a 250W motor; and offers a LED-backlit display and lunar bright headlight. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You have one question, though, before you launch full-fledged into your very first space age adventure. Just how far can you Glide? And more specifically, </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Can Scooters Go Long Distances?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is an important question to ask; one that should be answered before you go anywhere on your sharp new toy. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You don&rsquo;t want to get caught away from home or, heaven forbid, in the middle of the road, without a reliable form of transportation. And whenever you invest in any mode of transportation, recreational or otherwise, you need to know exactly how far it will take you.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is particularly true of scooters; transportation toys that find their origins in some highly rudimentary forms.</span></p>
<h1>The Razor Scooter</h1>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You remember the old school Razor scooter. Or, at least, your ankle does. Indeed, the old kick scooters of yesteryear were manually operated vehicles that more than lived up to their moniker. Riders most literally kicked off with one foot to guide and propel their ride; which tended to flow along very slowly and take them to the end of their driveway. Or, if they were feeling particularly adventurous that day, the southernmost border of their suburban neighborhood.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The GOTRAX GLIDER, however, is not your grandparents&rsquo; scooter. This is a veritable space-age vehicle that shines in its top-notch torque, self-balancing glide, fast fold and release, a smooth and speedy 3-2-1 liftoff, and a top-notch design that is both stunning and dynamic.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It makes sense that the GLIDER will take you places; taking you much farther, in fact, than any and all nonmotorized predecessors. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When riding a GLIDER, you can, in fact, GLIDE uninterrupted for 9.3 miles on a single complete charge; with this number depending on factors such as usage, climate, conditions, rider weight, riding style, and care and maintenance. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Just imagine the possibilities. In your life and living space, just how far could 9.3 miles take you? Around your own neighborhood, either garnering some prime alone time as you spread your wings and exercise&mdash;or perhaps spending quality time and running races with your equally sporty friends? Across closed courses and skate parks, where you can play and compete with the best of &lsquo;em? Even to work, via commutes that save big time on time and gas money? </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The truth is that your GLIDER will take you as far as your imagination&mdash;and your battery&mdash;will take you.</span></p>
<h1>How to Charge a Scooter Battery?</h1>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It will require about three hours to charge your GOTRAX GLIDER; this process is integral to the successful operation of the machine. It is important to recharge the battery after every ride, unplugging the charger from the wall once the charge is complete. Once the charge is full and the power switch is turned off, you can store the vehicle for extended periods of time. Then it will be ready to go whenever and wherever you go!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In order to charge the GOTRAX GLIDER, plug the provided charger and adapter&nbsp;into a grounded outlet (100V-240V; 50-60Hz).&nbsp;Then plug the opposite end of the charger/adapter into the battery charging port&nbsp;of the GOTRAX GLIDER, situated below the power button and toward the top of&nbsp;the handlebars behind a black rubber cover. The indicator light will turn red to confirm that the transportation toy is charging. The GLIDER battery is fully charged when the indicator light turns from&nbsp;red to green.&nbsp;&nbsp;Lastly, detach the charger/adapter from the GOTRAX GLIDER before activating&nbsp;or operating.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Also be sure to read and consult your GOTRAX Glider Electric Scooter Commander&rsquo;s Manual; a handy and complimentary guide that will teach you how to ride, clean and care for your intergalactic transportation toy. You can always go the distance on a well-maintained, well-tended vehicle; and by adhering to the guidelines outlined in the pages of your Commander&rsquo;s Manual, you can make your GoTrax GLIDER really go the distance.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The GLIDER Electric Scooter and other GoTrax space age recreational vehicles are designed for use on closed courses. So before you venture much beyond your own driveway, garage, yard, lot or rec room, be sure to consult your local Department of Motor Vehicles and learn the laws of your state and city in regard to the ownership and usage of electronic recreational vehicles.</span></p>
<p>If you still want to learn more about electric scooters check out our guide to finding the <a href="https://gotrax.com/news/best-electric-scooter-reviews/">best electric scooter</a>.</p>
<p><b>Regardless of how far you venture in the immense GoTrax universe, be sure to wear your helmet and obey the rules of the road. Oh, and have fun!</b></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/how-far-can-electric-scooters-go">Can Electric Scooters Go Long Distances?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Are Electric Scooters good for City Commutes?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/electric-scooters-for-city-commutes/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 21:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cambria Olsen]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=12548</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Life in the big city can be fun, exciting, downright inspirational, and even more downright frustrating; especially when one considers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/electric-scooters-for-city-commutes/">Are Electric Scooters good for City Commutes?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Life in the big city can be fun, exciting, downright inspirational, and even more downright frustrating; especially when one considers the problematic nature of big city commutes. Just imagine what seems like a bazillion individuals packed like sardines across three or four lanes of bumper to bumper traffic; their gassy automobiles filling the atmosphere with toxic exhaust fumes&mdash;as they themselves might fill the air with pointed, most likely unrepeatable words of advice for drivers who speed past them or cut them off at any given moment.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Every day, it seems, big city commutes rob us of our time, our gas money and our sanity. &nbsp;Really, though, what&rsquo;s the alternative?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Well, what if we were to tell you that a big city commute can be just as fun and fast-paced as the big city itself?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;A city commute, fun?!&rdquo; you might very well be thinking at this point. &ldquo;What madness do you speak here?!&rdquo;</span></p>
<h1>Enter the GOTRAX Glider Commuter Scooter</h1>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Well first off, let us establish the difference between driving to work and Gliding to work. &nbsp;When you Glide to work, you can sail effortless past those congested lanes and bask free in the open air; savoring the sight of both the towering skyscrapers and emerald greenspaces that typify the big city.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Today, more and more Earthlings are &lsquo;going galactic&rsquo; by riding their electric scooters to work. They are morphing their standard daily commutes into lightning fast, high-powered interplanetary adventures; saving time, energy and the environment as they come up with their own, far more enjoyable version of &lsquo;rush hour.&rsquo;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The GOTRAX GLIDER <a href="https://gotrax.com/shop/electric-scooters/glider/">Electric Scooter</a> just might be the ideal &lsquo;commuter scooter&rsquo;, a space-age vehicle that cruises at speeds up to 17 mph with a 250W motor and features a LED-backlit display and lunar bright headlight. Other deluxe features include top-notch torque, self-balancing glide, fast fold and release, a smooth and speedy 3-2-1 liftoff, and a top-notch design that is both stunning and dynamic.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A safer commute also is assured with the GLIDER Electric Scooter, which offers a hand-controlled brake and a foot-activated slowing system. &nbsp;And once you arrive at work, you can easily fold and store this interplanetary vehicle just as you would an umbrella; stowing it conveniently in any closet or even beneath your desk. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Yet before you hoist your auto to the nearest junkyard and cruise off into the sunset on your trusty scooter, just know that different regions of the country have varying laws and codes that apply to riding electric scooters in public; and big cities, in particular, may limit your use of electric scooters for the purpose of your commutes.</span></p>
<h1>Commuting on your GOTRAX Glider</h1>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Primarily designed for use on closed courses and away from busy roads, an electric scooter may not be ideal for all big city commutes. And some cities may require you to license yourself or your ride before Gliding forth into the inner-city galaxy.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Before you buy a GLIDER or other electric scooter, contact your local Department of Motor Vehicles and learn the laws of your state and city regarding the ownership and usage of electronic recreational vehicles&mdash;especially on big city streets.</span></p>
<h3>New York City</h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The NYC city council banned motorized scooters in 2004, initially restricting the ban to those scooters that traveled faster than 15 mph. The Council eliminated the speed criteria in 2013, effectively <a href="http://www.citylandnyc.org/scooters-hoverboards-bicycles-whats-legal/">banning all motorized scooters</a> on the streets of New York (</span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">NYC v. Onix Guzman</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">, ECB Appeal No. 1501125 (Dec. 17, 2015)).</span></p>
<h3>Calfornia</h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In California, riders do not have to register, license or insure motorized scooters, which may be operated on trails, bicycle paths or bikeways, and on the right-hand curb of roads where the speed limit does not exceed 25 mph.</span></p>
<h3>Florida</h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In Florida, state law dictates that &ldquo;Any vehicle not having a seat or saddle for the use of the rider, designed to travel on not more than three wheels, and not capable of propelling the vehicle at a speed greater than 30 mph is classified as a &ldquo;</span>motorized scooter<span style="font-weight: 400;">&rdquo; and is not allowed to be operated on the roadways,&rdquo; reports the Ride Two Wheels website. &nbsp;&ldquo;</span>Motor scooters&hellip;are motor vehicles, so they are allowed on Florida roadways, but must be titled and registered. Also, the driver must possess a valid driver&rsquo;s license.&rdquo;</p>
<h3>Texas</h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">And in Texas, a <a href="http://www.ridetwowheels.com/electric-scooters-adults-street-legal/">motorized scooter</a> can be ridden only on a highway or street where the stated speed limit is 35 mph or less; which might complicate the issue of big city commutes for Lone Star Commanders.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Even if you can&rsquo;t &lsquo;scoot&rsquo; through your &lsquo;commute,&rsquo; you may be able to Glide to your ride! Indeed, many people ride their electric scooters to their bus or train stops; and with the GLIDER&rsquo;s fast fold and release system, you can fold and store your scooter in just about any luggage compartment. &nbsp;Amtrak and other major transportation companies invite riders to bring their bike and scooters on board with them; thus facilitating long commutes.</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/electric-scooters-for-city-commutes/">Are Electric Scooters good for City Commutes?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Riding an Electric Scooter to Work Cheaper than Driving a Car?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/riding-electric-scooter-work-cheaper-driving-car/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 22:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cambria Olsen]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=12380</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Many of our GOTRAX commanders choose to ride one of our machines simply because it&#8217;s fun and easy to do. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/riding-electric-scooter-work-cheaper-driving-car/">Is Riding an Electric Scooter to Work Cheaper than Driving a Car?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Many of our GOTRAX commanders choose to ride one of our machines simply because it&rsquo;s fun and easy to do. But, riding an electric scooter to work or college could also save you money. You don&rsquo;t have to pay out for fuel, maintenance or repairs as you do for a car. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The cost of driving a car each day can be high. You have to pay for fuel. These costs can be especially high if your journey involves lots of stopping and starting, or changes in speed, as all of these results in more fuel being used. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You also have to pay for the regular maintenance of your vehicle, and any repairs that are necessary. This is before you pay out for additional costs such as a insurance. If your work or college is too far away for you to walk, then driving may seem like the obvious answer.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The truth is that hopping on board a GOTRAX GLIDER electric scooter might be a better idea. You don&rsquo;t have to pay out for fuel. All you have to do is make sure that the scooter is charged before you set off. Your machine is also easy to maintain, and you aren&rsquo;t faced with the cost of having to make sure that a lot of parts are kept in good working order. Of course, you can still use your car for long journeys. But, if you&rsquo;re only traveling a couple of miles to work and back, you can do so on a GOTRAX electric scooter with no problem.</span></p>
<h1>More than Money</h1>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It&rsquo;s not just about saving money either. It can also work out quicker to use an electric scooter to travel to work. All of our commanders know how easy it is to navigate the galaxy on a GOTRAX Glider. You can zip in and out of obstacles, at speeds of up to 17 mph. It&rsquo;s also easy to get around corners with no extra effort required. This means that you can avoid getting stuck in long queues of traffic. You can get where you need to be quicker, as well as more cost-effectively. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you think that it&rsquo;s too far for you to travel all the way to work on an electric scooter, you can combine using a GOTRAX Glider with using public transport. You can step on your machine, and glide through the universe until you reach the bus stop, then you can simply fold away the scooter and jump on the bus. The team of experts at GOTRAX Command have ensured that all machines are designed to be easily folded away and released. This means that your GOTRAX Glider can be easily carried while you are using public transport. It also means that you can safely store your machine under your desk if you use it on your commute to work. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">All of this means that you can save on the amount of fuel you use for your own vehicle. This helps you to save money and is also good for the environment.</span></p>
<h1>Get Outside</h1>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On top of these obvious benefits, commanding a GOTRAX Glider electric scooter on a regular basis can also be good for your health. Riding an electric scooter cannot be described as strenuous exercise, but it can help you to start becoming more active. You use your body as you navigate your way around corners and obstacles, and the very fact that you stand for a period of time, rather than sitting, is a good thing. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Starting to use a GOTRAX Glider machine on your daily commute helps to get you to use the car less, which automatically starts to make you more active. You can walk part of the way to work, while still having your electric scooter to hand, to help you out should the exercise start to get too much for you. Learning to rely less on your car to get around is a good thing when it comes to your health. Using a GOTRAX Glider electric scooter can help you with this. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One of the best things about the GOTRAX Glider is that it&rsquo;s really easy to ride. Unlike learning to drive, you don&rsquo;t need lessons. You can just step onto the machine, and set off on your galactic exploration. You have complete control over your machine, so you are safe at all times. To slow down, you can either use a foot-activated breaking device or the electric&nbsp;handbrake. There is also a throttle to use which helps you to regulate the speed you are traveling at. It&rsquo;s that simple. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">GOTRAX Glider <a href="https://gotrax.com/shop/electric-scooters/glider/">electric scooter</a> also look cool. They come in a range of colors, including Nebula Black, Pulsar Pink, and Mars Red. Much like you can when you buy a car, you can choose the color that best suits you. It&rsquo;s easy to choose the machine that you want. You just need to visit the GOTRAX Command Centre online. All of the machines in the fleet are available to buy on the website. You can also buy GOTRAX rideables at Walmart, Amazon and Dunham&rsquo;s Sports. You just take a look at the range and choose the electric scooter that best suits what you are looking for. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Once you have purchased your GOTRAX Glider electric scooter, you can use it to have fun exploring the universe. Or, you can use it to travel to work and back each day. Doing this can save you money on the fuel you have to buy for your car. It can also save wear and tear on your vehicle, meaning you spend less on maintenance and repairs. </span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/riding-electric-scooter-work-cheaper-driving-car/">Is Riding an Electric Scooter to Work Cheaper than Driving a Car?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Electric Scooters are Best for Adults?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/best-electric-scooters-for-adults/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 21:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cambria Olsen]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=12378</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>As a child, you may very well have enjoyed your good old-fashioned kick scooter; a cute, quaint little toy that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/best-electric-scooters-for-adults/">What Electric Scooters are Best for Adults?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As a child, you may very well have enjoyed your good old-fashioned kick scooter; a cute, quaint little toy that scooted you around your own small neighborhood at a leisurely pace.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We&rsquo;re sure that you have fond memories of your beloved little plaything; one that you have long since put away in the recesses of your attic or garage alongside your tricycle, your bike with the training wheels (yep, admit it; you know you had it. We all did!), and other fond but no longer usable mementoes of a quieter, easier life.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Because let&rsquo;s face it: Nothing about your life today is in any manner quiet or easy. You very likely begin and end the day with a fast-paced commute to your place of business. &nbsp;And on the weekends, you no longer scoot; you race, you run, you compete&hellip;and you glide.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You rarely invest in transportation toys; and when you do, the easygoing, slow-moving scooter is far from your first choice.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Well what if we were to tell you that one particular variety of scooter is fun and awesome enough for a kid&mdash;but intense, hard driving, and high flying enough for an adult? &nbsp;And what if we were to divulge further that, in addition to scooting along with this space-age transportation toy, you can </span><b>glide </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">on it as well? </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The GOTRAX GLIDER <a href="https://gotrax.com/shop/electric-scooters/glider/">Electric Scooter</a> is a celestial vehicle that is&mdash;to put it simply&mdash;heads and tail lights above others of its kind; and in a vast variety of ways. &nbsp;And it is the perfect scooter for the modern adult.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/best-electric-scooters-for-adults/">What Electric Scooters are Best for Adults?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Does Riding an Electric Scooter Count as Exercise?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/riding-electric-scooter-as-exercise/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 20:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cambria Olsen]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=12376</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Taking a journey on a GOTRAX GLIDER electric scooter is not rigorous exercise. But, it does mean that you are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/riding-electric-scooter-as-exercise/">Does Riding an Electric Scooter Count as Exercise?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Taking a journey on a <a href="https://gotrax.com/shop/electric-scooters/glider/">GOTRAX GLIDER electric scooter</a> is not rigorous exercise. But, it does mean that you are standing, and moving your body, rather than sitting down in one position. It&rsquo;s an excellent way of getting your body moving and enjoying the fresh air, even if you are not able to exercise rigorously. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One of the main aims of a GOTRAX GLIDER is to ensure that all of our curious commanders can explore new places, easily and quickly. This means that using a GOTRAX electric scooter is not a strenuous process. This doesn&rsquo;t mean that riding your machine is not good for you. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Once you step onto a GOTRAX electric scooter, you need to stand up for the rest of the journey. You also need to move your body to match the movement of the scooter, as you turn corners and move around obstacles. These actions mean that you expend more energy than you would by&nbsp;sitting around in one place. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is a good thing because sitting for long periods of time can be really bad for your health. It can cause you to become overweight, or even obese. It can also lead to health issues such as type II diabetes and certain types of cancer. Medical experts recommend that you should move as much as possible each day. They suggest activities such as walking to work or college instead of taking a bus, or even just walking up and down stairs instead of taking the elevator. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Stepping on a GOTRAX GLIDER electric scooter, and setting off exploring the galaxy, can be a great way of starting to introduce exercise into your life. You get to be more active, without having to take on anything more testing, until you are ready. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you want to start building up the amount of exercise you&rsquo;re doing, while still enjoying the thrill of zipping around on your craft, you can glide for a while, then simply fold up your GOTRAX GLIDER, and carry it with you while you walk quickly for a while. Then, you can simply release your machine, and glide off back to home base. The great thing about GOTRAX electric scooters is that they are designed to be easy to fold and release. This means that you can take all of these actions with no hassle.</span></p>
<h1>Exercise &amp; Fresh Air</h1>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You should also remember that getting fresh air, while you are on your galactic explorations, is good for your health. This is why it&rsquo;s a good idea to try and ride your machine in parks, or fields, away from the fumes of traffic passing by. Fresh air is good for you for several reasons. It helps to increase the flow of oxygen around your body. Increases in oxygen levels can help to improve blood pressure issues and give a boost to your immune system. The increase also helps your lungs to perform better and helps you to think more clearly. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So, if you have a decision to make, why not head off on a journey on your electric scooter, and get the fresh air you need to help you think more clearly. The fresh air should also help you to feel happier. We know that most of our commanders think that the GOTAX GLIDER also helps with your happiness rating. You can take off on your own, and explore, at a speed of up to 17mph. It&rsquo;s an exhilarating way to spend some time. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So, although riding an electric scooter is not classed as an exercise regime itself, it can help. You get to start being more active, and you can integrate other activities, such as walking, into your regular GOTRAX GLIDER adventures. This helps you to have fun while also improving your health. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you want to start walking to work or college, and it&rsquo;s just a bit too far to manage, to start with, why not use a GOTRAX GLIDER to help. You can start off by walking as far as you&rsquo;re comfortable with, carrying your machine. Then, if you start to struggle, you can release the GOTRAX GLIDER, and glide along for a while. If the weather is bad on the way home, and you don&rsquo;t want to walk, you can simply ride your electric scooter to the stop, and jump on a bus. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Don&rsquo;t forget that, if you&rsquo;re not used to exercising, it&rsquo;s good to start slowly. Your GOTRAX GLIDER can help you to do this.</span></p>
<h1>Fun is Healthy too</h1>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Exploring the universe on your machine is also a fun activity in its own right. You may not think it, but this fun can be just as good for you as exercise. People often become too busy with life to actually have fun. But, not finding time for fun in your life can often lead to you feeling more stressed. You can also start to feel anxious and depressed. This is why having some fun in your life is so important. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The GOTRAX GLIDER electric scooter is designed so that it&rsquo;s easy to get around. You don&rsquo;t have to exert much energy to ride one of the GOTRAX machines. But, stepping on an electric scooter is still a lot better than sitting around reading, watching TV or playing video games. It can get you outside and into some fresh air. It can also be a great way of starting to get more active, leading you to take more exercise overall. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you want to exercise more, make sure that you start to include activities, such as walking, into the GOTRAX GLIDER galactic journeys that you enjoy so much. By doing this you can keep having all the fun, and improve your health at the same time. &nbsp;</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/riding-electric-scooter-as-exercise/">Does Riding an Electric Scooter Count as Exercise?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Can I ride an electric scooter without a license?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/ride-electric-scooter-without-license/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 00:22:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Vasanth]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=12329</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#160; So you stand as the proud new owner of a GOTRAX GLIDER Electric Scooter. And as a newly minted [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/ride-electric-scooter-without-license/">Can I ride an electric scooter without a license?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>So you stand as the proud new owner of a GOTRAX GLIDER Electric Scooter. And as a newly minted Commander, you simply can&rsquo;t wait to GLIDE along on your elaborate and exciting new transportation toy; a space-age vehicle that launches you into the galaxy at speeds up to 17 mph with a 250W motor&mdash;lighting your way with a LED-backlit display and lunar bright headlight. And you can practically taste the GLIDER&rsquo;s top-notch torque, smooth self-balancing glide, swift fold and release, a dramatic 3-2-1 liftoff, and a splendid design that is both stunning and dynamic.</p>
<p>You simply cannot wait to cruise the universe on the waves of your celestial GLIDER, but wait a minute. Did you know that, in some states and under certain conditions, you actually might need a license to operate an electric scooter?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/ride-electric-scooter-without-license/">Can I ride an electric scooter without a license?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Can you Take an Electric Scooter on a Train?</title>
		<link>https://gotrax.com/support/faq/electric-scooter-train</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2018 00:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Diandra]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gotrax.com/?post_type=faqs&#038;p=12099</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;ll need to verify directly with the train station, but in general, the safety requirements for trains are less strict [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/electric-scooter-train">Can you Take an Electric Scooter on a Train?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>You&rsquo;ll need to verify directly with the train station, but in general, the safety requirements for trains are less strict than those of airplanes. So it may be possible for you to take your <a href="https://gotrax.com/shop/electric-scooters/glider/">GOTRAX GLIDER electric scooter</a> on a train. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com/support/faq/electric-scooter-train">Can you Take an Electric Scooter on a Train?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://gotrax.com">GOTRAX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
